{
    "questionsData":[
        {"question":"Bok", "answer":"Hi", "nValue": 1, "position": 1}, 
        {"question":"Kako se zovete?", "answer":"What's your name?", "nValue": 1, "position": 2},
        {"question":"Kako ste?", "answer":"How are you?", "nValue": 1, "position": 3},
        {"question":"Razumijem", "answer":"I understand", "nValue": 1, "position": 4}, 
        {"question":"Ne razumijem", "answer":"I don't understand", "nValue": 1, "position": 5},
        {"question":"Dobrodošli", "answer":"Welcome", "nValue": 1, "position": 6},
        {"question":"Doviđenja", "answer":"Goodbye", "nValue": 1, "position": 7},
        {"question":"Molim", "answer":"Please", "nValue": 1, "position": 8},
        {"question":"Ispričavam se", "answer":"Excuse me", "nValue": 1, "position": 9},
        {"question":"Dobar tek", "answer":"Have a nice meal", "nValue": 1, "position": 10},
        {"question":"Sretno", "answer":"Good luck", "nValue": 1, "position": 11},
        {"question":"Uzdravlje!", "answer":"Cheers", "nValue": 1, "position": 12}
    ]
}